<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">India Receives First Rafale</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Rajnath in France</string>
    <string name="article_text">AThe Indian Air Force on Tuesday received its first Rafale fighter jet from a series of 36 aircraft purchased from France in the presence of Defence Minister Rajnath Singh here.
                                Asim Umar, a Pakistani citizen, “was #killed along with six other AQIS members, most of them Pakistani”, in southern Helmand Province, the National Directorate of Security said on Twitter, adding that Umar had been “embedded” in a Taliban compound.
                                The leader of al-Qaeda in the Indian Subcontinent (AQIS) was killed in a joint U.S.-Afghan operation in September, Afghan officials confirmed on October 8.
                                Durga Puja celebrations this year were about more than just colours and creativity. Moving away from the customary themes, organisers this year experimented with socio-political and environmental issues.
                                From depicting the refugee crisis due to the implementation of the National Register of Citizens, to paying homage to soldiers killed in the Pulwama attack, theme-based pandals this year were major crowd-pullers.
                                Shah Rukh Khan’s connect with Tamil Nadu goes a long way... he even named one of his films Chennai Express. He is good friends with most of the Tamil superstars, especially Rajinikanth and Kamal Haasan. In fact, he even roped in Rajinikanth for a cameo in Ra.One. Currently, there is unverified news that Shah Rukh might be making a cameo in the Vijay-starrer Bigil.
                                During a recent interaction with his fans on Twitter, the Bollywood star has revealed his directorial plans. When a user asked him, “Do you have any plan to direct a Tamil movie in future?,” he replied, albeit in a lighter vein, “Of course!! My command over the language is so good!!”
                                Among other things, the actor was full of praise for Tamil stars. When someone asked him to comment about Dhanush, he said, “I love him” and described as ‘awesome’ the interactions he has had with Vijay.
                                Shah Rukh Khan’s connect with Tamil Nadu goes a long way... he even named one of his films Chennai Express. He is good friends with most of the Tamil superstars, especially Rajinikanth and Kamal Haasan. In fact, he even roped in Rajinikanth for a cameo in Ra.One. Currently, there is unverified news that Shah Rukh might be making a cameo in the Vijay-starrer Bigil.
                                </string>
    <string name="add_comment">Add Comment</string>
</resources>
